{
  "LevelId": 40,
  "Questions": [
    {
      "id": 408,
      "level_image": 6,
      "answer_text": "CABALETTA",
      "question": "term for a vocal piece in opera characterized by a lively and rhythmically-driven style,"
    },
    {
      "id": 409,
      "level_image": 6,
      "answer_text": "HYDROXIDE",
      "question": "chemical term for an ion composed of one oxygen atom and one hydrogen atom,"
    },
    {
      "id": 410,
      "level_image": 6,
      "answer_text": "KRUMMHOLZ",
      "question": "German word is used to describe the twisted, stunted trees often found in alpine"
    },
    {
      "id": 411,
      "level_image": 6,
      "answer_text": "QUANTIZER",
      "question": "algorithm that converts a continuous range of input values into a discrete set of output values"
    },
    {
      "id": 412,
      "level_image": 6,
      "answer_text": "PIGGYBACK",
      "question": "describe the practice of carrying or transporting one thing on the back of another,"
    },
    {
      "id": 413,
      "level_image": 6,
      "answer_text": "BABBLINGS",
      "question": "term for incoherent or meaningless speech,"
    },
    {
      "id": 414,
      "level_image": 6,
      "answer_text": "QUICKTIME",
      "question": "interactive content formats, often associated with the .mov file extension"
    },
    {
      "id": 415,
      "level_image": 6,
      "answer_text": "VOLATILES",
      "question": "compounds that have a tendency to vaporize or evaporate at relatively low temperatures"
    },
    {
      "id": 416,
      "level_image": 6,
      "answer_text": "BABYDOLLS",
      "question": "term is commonly used to refer to short, sleeveless, and loose-fitting nightgowns or dresses,"
    },
    {
      "id": 417,
      "level_image": 6,
      "answer_text": "BLINDNESS",
      "question": "condition is characterized by the inability to see"
    },
    {
      "id": 418,
      "level_image": 0,
      "answer_text": "EXHIBITION",
      "question": "used to describe a public display or show, often organized to showcase art,"
    }
  ]
}